http://www.hotpepperinc.com/privacy.html

Privacy
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS AND PRIVACY STATEMENT
Privacy Statement Hot Pepper Technology has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. We intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information (individually identifiable information about an individual collected online) and strive to help you protect your privacy while using our services. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone. Please read this notice. By using this site, you signify your consent to our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site:
www.HotPepperInc.com
Information Collection and Use Hot Pepper Technology is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others.
Registration In order to use some portions of this web site, a user must first complete the
registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the products and services offered by Hot Pepper Technology.
Warning: The elements of this web site, including graphics, logos, images, designs, sounds, information, and documents (the "Materials"), are protected by copyright, trademark, trade dress, trade secret, unfair competition and other laws and are owned by Hot Pepper Technology Inc. and its subsidiaries, divisions and affiliates ("Hot Pepper Technology"); or its suppliers, vendors or other third parties who have contributed Materials to the web site (each a "Supplier"). In no event shall any of the Materials be copied, reproduced, distributed, displayed, downloaded, stored in a retrieval system, or transmitted in any form without the prior express written permission of Hot Pepper Technology and/or its Supplier.
EMail Detective - Forensic Software Tool™, eChat Locker®, Hot Pepper
Technology® and other Hot Pepper Technology products and brands mentioned in this web site are registered trademarks or trademarks of Hot Pepper Technology in the United States and/or other countries. The names of actual products and companies mentioned in this web site may be registered trademarks or trademarks of their respective owners.
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
General Disclaimer
THE MATERIALS ON THIS WEBSITE COULD INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS AND ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE AT ANY TIME.
THE MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, Hot Pepper Technology AND ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, AND CONDITIONS WITH RESPECT TO THE MATERIALS, THEIR QUALITY, PERFORMANCE, SUITABILITY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT WILL Hot Pepper Technology AND ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT OR TORT, ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE MATERIALS AVAILABLE ON THIS WEBSITE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IN PARTICULAR, AND WITHOUT LIMITATION, Hot Pepper Technology SHALL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR ANY LOSS OF USE, DATA, INCLUDING THE COSTS OF RECOVERING SUCH DATA, OR PROFITS.
Order Information We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this information is used to contact the user.
Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Security
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the industry standard - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representatives) are granted access to personally identifiable information.  Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added; our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our web site, you can send an email to
legal@HotPepperInc.com
Software and Training Updates We also send the user product and service announcement updates. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and information via email.
Notification of Changes If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes here on our Privacy page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Web pages and content Copyright © 2003- by
Hot Pepper Technology, Inc.
Privacy    |    Usage Mark
siteuptime
